authorizedstream.com 2014-11-23

# 

**AuthorizedStream.com Privacy Policy**

Policy last updated December 5, 2012 

This is the Privacy Policy for the www.AuthorizedStream.com website, the AuthorizedStream mobile app and any media application using the AuthorizedStream Service (as defined in the Terms of Use). 

Your Acceptance of this Privacy Policy 

By using the AuthorizedStream Service, including, without limitation, responding to offers, exchanging information about your personal preferences, and continuing to receive information from AuthorizedStream, you agree to accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information as described herein. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms of Use which is incorporated herein by this reference. 

Information We Collect. 

If you choose to share your personal information with us we will collect and retain information that may personally identify you (such as your name, location, mobile device identifier, physical address, telephone number, email address, billing information, or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information). 

If you decide not to register or provide such information, you may not be able to use certain features of the Service or other services. 

Even if you choose not to share your personal information, we may automatically collect non-personal information, including, but not limited to, IP (internet protocol) address, location, ISP (internet service provider), the Web browser used to visit the AuthorizedStream Service, length and time of visit, the pages visited, a unique mobile device identifier and other usage data AuthorizedStream may collect from time to time. 

We use "cookies" (small files placed on your computer to help optimize performance), single pixel GIF image files (also called “Pixels” or "Web beacons"), Web server log analysis and other similar technologies, and other tracking technology (such as Flash Persistent Storage) that help us manage and track your interaction with the AuthorizedStream Service. We may share such information with third parties. 

We track the music played through the AuthorizedStream Service and report it to our third party partners in the aggregate in order to meet their obligation to report and pay copyright owners and for other lawful uses, including analytics and marketing undertaken by those third parties. These reports do not contain personally-identifiable information. 

We work with third party online advertising networks to deliver advertising on the AuthorizedStream Service. Such third parties may utilize cookies or other tracking and targeting technologies. We are not responsible for information collected by third party advertisers in this manner, nor for the collection or use of information by other sites to which the AuthorizedStream Service is linked. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers, ad networks, and websites for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Any data obtained by third-party ad servers subsequently shared with us is maintained and dealt with by us in accordance with this privacy policy. When you access the AuthorizedStream Service through a service partner, we may add your email address or other personalized information, so that we can identify which of our service partners or other sign-in pages to send to you when you log on. 

We may also collect information about the devices you use to access the AuthorizedStream Service. This information may include your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. We also may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device or other transactional information for that device. 

Information We Receive From Third Parties 

We may receive information about you from third parties and store it in our databases with personally identifiable information that you provide to us. These third parties may include advertisers that make features available through the AuthorizedStream Service, access partners, and marketing companies that create or sell other marketing data. AuthorizedStream is only responsible for abiding by its own privacy policy and will assume no liability if a business partner or other entity collects, uses or shares any information about you in violation of its own privacy policy or applicable law. 

Use of Information 

We use your personal information and non-personal information to provide you with services, to notify you of new products or services, and communicate with you. We also use the information that we collect for the following purposes: 

• To customize and personalize the advertising and the content you see and hear.  
• To enhance the listener experience in our network of websites and broadcasts. We use tracking information to enhance our offering.  
• To fulfill your requests to receive information or services and permit you to interact with the AuthorizedStream Service.  
• To send you alerts on developments and features that may be of interest.

Consent to Sharing Information 

We may rent, sell, and share your personal information and non-personal information with our network partners and third-party affiliates for the purposes of direct mail, email marketing, mobile marketing, and telemarketing. Additionally, we may share such personal information with the broadcaster to whose station you use. 

By providing personal information to us you agree:  
• all information you have provided is true and correct to the best of your knowledge;  
• you are establishing a business relationship with AuthorizedStream and with its marketing partners; and  
• you are requesting and expressly consenting to be contacted via telephone (whether wireless or wired), including by live or prerecorded, calls using an automated dialing system, email, and/or mail by us, our network partners, and third-party affiliates and marketing partners regardless of whether your telephone number is on any Do Not Call list(s)  
• From time to time, we may establish a business relationship with other businesses and third party marketing partners whom we believe trustworthy and who have confirmed that their privacy practices are consistent with ours ("Service Providers"). For example, we may contract with Service Providers and third-party marketing partners to provide certain services, such as hosting and maintenance, customer relationship management, data storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We provide our Service Providers and/or third-party marketing partners with the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each Service Provider and/or third-party marketing partner must agree to use reasonable security procedures and practices, appropriate to the nature of the information involved, in order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. 

We may work with third-party marketing and advertising companies ("Ad Networks"). These companies may collect and use information about your use of the AuthorizedStream Service or services in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Advertisements may be shown via the AuthorizedStream Service, the services, or third-party sites. These companies may use cookies or other tracking technologies. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that an Ad Network may collect from you. It also does not cover any information that you may choose to provide to an Ad Network or to an advertiser whose goods or services are advertised through the Service. For such information, you are subject to the terms of the Ad Networks’ privacy policy. We may share personal information and non-personal information with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with AuthorizedStream. If AuthorizedStream is merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we may disclose or transfer personal information and non-personal information in connection with such transaction. We shall also cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose personal information and non-personal information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property or rights of AuthorizedStream or of any third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law. 

Children's Privacy 

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we receive personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records once we learn of it. 

External Links 

The Service may contain links to other sites, or allow others to send you such links. A link to a third party's site does not mean that we endorse it or that we are affiliated with it. We do not exercise control over third-party sites. You access such third-party sites or content at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third-party site before providing any information to the site. 

Opting Out 

AuthorizedStream uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, go to: [networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Contacting Us 

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, you may write to us at: AuthorizedStream Data Privacy, 345 Sheridan Avenue, Suite 421, Palo Alto, CA 94306. 

Please provide complete information to facilitate your request, as well as your complete contact information. 

Privacy Policy Changes 

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the AuthorizedStream Service. Those changes will go into effect on the revision date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the AuthorizedStream Service constitutes your consent to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. 

Your California Privacy Rights 

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for such third parties' direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to: 

FreeStreams, Inc.,   
Attn: Data Privacy,  
345 Sheridan Avenue, Suite 421  
Palo Alto, CA 94306
